qanvast.com 2018-11-30

# Privacy Policy | Qanvast - Interior Design & Renovation Ideas

**Qanvast is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this site (the "Site").** This Privacy Policy applies to the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to other web sites to which we link. You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

If you choose to use Qanvast, we may require you to provide personal information as indicated on the Qanvast site, whether as part of the registration process or in connection with your use of the Qanvast site.

 **We collect and store the following information:**

  * Email address, IP address, and physical contact information;
  * Comments, reviews, images, other uploaded content, questions and answers, discussion area posts and other messages, including correspondence between Qanvast and you; and
  * Other information automatically collected whenever you interact with Qanvast, such as computer sign-on data, statistics on page views and traffic to and from the Qanvast site. For example, we use "cookies" (small data files that are placed on your computer) so that we can recognize your browser and record such interaction information. You can disable the use of cookies through your browser settings, however this is likely to affect your ability to use certain features of the Qanvast site.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use the Qanvast site or services.

 **We may use your information as follows:**

  * to provide Qanvast services;
  * to verify your identity when you sign in;
  * to encourage safe online experiences and enforce our policies;
  * to customize users' experience, analyze site usage, improve and measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;
  * to identify your reviews as your own;
  * to communicate administrative announcements when we need to provide users with information that may affect their use of Qanvast;
  * to communicate marketing and promotional offers to our users;
  * to provide customer service; and
  * to deliver to you information that is targeted to your interests. Upon receipt of the first communication of this type, you will have the opportunity to opt-out of future communications by following unsubscribe instructions described within the communication. As part of your registration on Qanvast, you agree that you may receive certain administrative communications from Qanvast, and you will not be able to opt out of receiving such administrative communications.

 **We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. However, we may disclose your personal information as follows:**

to affiliates of Qanvast that we control and that are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow privacy practices at least as protective; to identify your reviews as your own; to third parties to enforce our Terms of Use and other Qanvast agreements and policies, or to protect anyone's rights, property, or safety; to third parties to respond to claims that photos or other content that you upload violates other's rights; to an acquirer of all or substantially all of the equity, assets or business of Qanvast; to service providers who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of Qanvast services under obligations of confidentiality; to law enforcement or other government officials in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities; as otherwise required by law.

To prevent unauthorized access, promote data security, and encourage appropriate use of information, we use a variety of tools to assist in the protection of your personal information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, so we are not able to make any guarantees.

You agree that we may transfer your personal information to other countries as required in connection with any of the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may provide links to websites operated by companies other than Qanvast that we believe may be of interest to you. Except as set forth above, we do not disclose your personal information to the operators of such third-party websites without obtaining your consent. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third-party sites. If you choose to visit one of these third-party sites, you should review the privacy policy posted on such third-party site to understand how that party collects, uses and discloses your personal information.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [heretohelp@qanvast.com ](mailto:heretohelp@qanvast.com)
